# AHMET CAN ÇAKIR

Software Engineer





Hello my name is Ahmet Can. I'am 21 years old. I use a computer since my childhood. I was always wondering how to work softwares. I start coding to high school (14 years old). First my begining to language C# console app.3 months later level up and form app.I watch a lot of science fiction movies.Iron Man movie is change my mind and life.I saw JARVIS and I'm wondering it be possible. I started first search i so hard to search because not any have information my language and no any one help to me but I'm stubborn. I always think is if we can dream or thinking is can possible in to real life. Finally i make it to EMILY this program made C# can be speech recognition, face recognition, search on the web. This project approved to Erasmus+,

<u>TÜBİTAK (Scientific and Technological Research Council of Turkey)</u>. Took me to Erasmus Belgium, Netherlands i made a presentation.

## WORK EXPERIENCES

#### Software Engineer

Cikotvau | 2020 - Present

I programing to CRM.I use programming language to Python,PHP,HTML,CSS,JS.I use framework and library to OpenCV,Tesseract OCR,Selenium,BeautifulSoup,Codelgnither,Jquery...

- Machine Learning use to Data Analysing.
- CRM.
- E-Commerce.

#### **Software Developer**

Foriba(SOVOS) | 2020 - 2020

I was started web programming this company and i work on the ERP,CRM,CMS.

- GelsinMenu QR Restaurant Menu.
- <u>Majistral Reçete</u> Prescription system used by pharmacists
- HesapTut ERP pre-accounting program
- ERC SOFT Company Website

#### **Software Developer**

NKR | 2019 - 2019

I programming to car recognition on the Python,C++.Deep learning firt detect car to live image second classification to detect third find to brand and models and recognition plate.

# **Intern Software Developer**

TKGM | 2015 - 2016

Turkey general directorate of land registry cadastre i was intern.

## **Backend Developer**

INTA Engineering | 2015 - 2015

I was work IT specialist.

## SKILLS

#### Technical

JavaScript/Jquery

PHP/Codelgnither

PostgreSQL/MySQL

Python/C++

C#/Java

Android App/IOS app Matlab/R

#### **Professional**

Effective communication

Team player

# Strong problem solver

Good time management

# **EDUCATION**

### **Degree in Managment**

**Information Systems** Anadolu University

2020 - Present

#### **Associate Degree in Computer Programming**

**Baskent University** 2018 - 2020

# LANGUAGES

Turkish (Native)

English (Professional)

# INTERESTS

Make to Electronic Music

Taekwondo

Travelling